Beegle, Claire H. Papers 5271
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Claire H. Beegle Papers
1901-1960
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Beegle, Clair H.
5271
0.5 cubic feet
0.5 linear ft.
Papers (documents).
Printed materials related to U.S. railroads, including rule books, reports, and pamphlets.
8209516
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, November 12, 2013
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 08, 2019
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of printed materials related to U.S. railroads, including rule books, reports, and pamphlets. Railroads represented include the Pennsylvania Railroad;Chicago, Milwaukee, and St. Paul Railroad; Chicago, Rock Island, and Pacific Railway; and Northern Pacific Railway.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Beegle, Clair H.; Switchmen's Union of North America
8209516
- Rule book receipts, 1904 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Group insurance resolution, 1927 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Altoona Railroad Club of the Pennsylvania Railroad, 1908 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Report of Joint Committees on "Track" and "Yard Operations" on "The Modern Railroad Yard for Classification Purposes, Its Design and Operation." November 18, 1908., Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Scope and Contents
    By The Altoona Railraod Club of the Pennsylvania Railroad. Item is in English.
- Altoona Lodge, 1932; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Switchmen's Union of North America to Install Local Lodge in Altoona, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    By Switchmen's Union of North America (SUNA). Item is in English.
- Interstate Commerce Commission, 1910-1956; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Order: In Re Standard Height of Drawbars, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By Edward A. Moseley. October 10, 1910. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: In the Matter of Requiring an Increase in the Minimum Percentage of Power Brakes, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By Edward A. Moseley. June 6, 1910. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Order: In the Matter of the Method and Form of Monthly Reports of Hours of Service of Employees on Railroads Subject to the Act of March 4, 1907, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By Judson C. Clements. June 28, 1911. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Order: In the Matter of Alteration in the Method and Form of Monthly Reports of Hours of Service of Employees on Railroads Subject to the Act of March 4, 1907, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By John H. Marble. April 8, 1912. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: An Act Requiring Common Carriers Engaged in Interstate and Foreign Commerce to Make Full Reports of all Accidents to the Interstate Commerce Commission, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By United States Congress. May 6, 1910. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Hours-Of-Service Act (As Amended): An Act To Promote the Safety of Employees and Travelers Upon Railroads by Limiting the Hours of Service of Employees Thereon, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By United States Congress. March 4, 1907, as amended May 4, 1916. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Safety Appliance Acts, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By Interstate Commerce Commission (ICC). Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Order: In the Matter of Method and Form of Records to be Kept by Carriers Relating to the Time on Duty of Employees and the Movement of Trains, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By George B. McGinty. May 2, 1921. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Hours of Service Reports, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By Interstate Commerce Commission (ICC). Form of 1912. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Order: In the Matter of Designating the Number, Dimensions, Location, and Manner of Application of Certain Safety Appliances, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By Edward A. Moseley. March 13, 1911. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Hours of Srrrvice Report, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By Interstate Commerce Commission (ICC). Forms 1-8. Blank forms. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Accident at Woodbridge, N.J., Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By W. P. Bartel. Accident occurred on February 6, 1951. Decided on April 19, 1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: In Re Accident at Redondo Junction, Los Angeles, CA, on January 22, 1956., Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By Harold D. McCoy. Report on. 3675. Atchison, Topeka, and Santa Fe Railway Company. Decided March 15, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Report of the Director of the Bureau of Safety in re Investigation of an Accident Which Occurred on the Pennsylvania Railroad Near Gallitzin, PA, on December 9, 1931., Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By W. P. Borland. January 18, 1932. Item is in English.
- U.S. House of Representatives H.R. 17201, 1931; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: A Bill to Establish a Uniform Retirement System for Interstate Railroad Employees, and for Other Purposes, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    By US House of Representatives. H.R. 17201. February 20, 1931. Item is in English.
- Employee passes, 1905-1960; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Chicago, Milwaukee, and St. Paul Railway booklets, 1913-1920; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Special Rules and Instructions Covering Electrical Operation, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    By Chicago, Milwaukee & St. Paul Railroad (Lines West of Mobridge). January 20, 1920. For the Government and Information of Employes. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Instructions to Man Operating Dynamos on Electric Lighted Trains, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    By Chicago, Milwaukee & St. Paul Railroad. February 1920. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Tacoma Eastern Railroad Rulings on Schedule for Train and Yard Men, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    By Chicago, Milwaukee & St. Paul Railroad (Puget Sound Lines). Issued September 1, 1913. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Tacoma Eastern Railroad Schedule for Train and Yard Men, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    By Chicago, Milwaukee & St. Paul Railroad (Puget Sound Lines). Rates and rules will take effect January 28, 1913. Item is in English.
- Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific Railway, Local Passenger Tariff No. 12-21, 1937; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: One-Way First-Class and Coach Fares, also Milage Between Stations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    By Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific Railway Company. Local Passenger Tariff no.12-12. Issued May 25, 1937, Effective July 1, 1937. Item is in English.
- Northern Pacific Railroad Transportation rules, 1919; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Transportation Rules, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    By Northern Pacific Railroad. Train Rules, Block Signal Rules, Interlocking Rules, Signal Indications and Aspects, General Regulations. Item is in English.
- Pennsylvania lines west of Pittsburgh rules, 1901; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Rules of the Pennsylvania Lines West of Pittsburgh, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    By Pennsylvania Railroad. Effective April 1, 1901. Item is in English.
- Rock Island lines rules, 1922-1948; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: On The Human Side of Railroading, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    By J. E. Gorman. Reprint of brief messages to employes by J. E. Gorman, President of the Rock Island Lines, which have appeared from time to time in the Rock Island Magazine. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: To You Who Have Just Joined the Rock Island Family, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    By Rock Island Lines. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Rules and Regulations for Conductors, Train Auditors, and Collectors, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    By Rock Island Lines. Relating to handling of passes and revenue transportation and the preparation of reports to Auditor Passenger Traffic. Re-issued January 1, 1939. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Rules and Instructions Governing Employes in the Operation and Adjustment of Train Air Brakes, Air Signal, Heating, Ventilating, and Illuminating Appliances, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    By Rock Island Lines. Sixth edition. Effective September 1, 1922. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Rock Island Lines News Digest, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    By Rock Island Lines. v.7:no.12 (1948: Dec.). Item is in English.
- Rock Island lines, combination freight train and wheel report, 1930; Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Combination Freight Train and Wheel Report, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    By Rock Island Lines. Blank forms. Item is in English.
- Union Pacific Railroad booklets, 1941; Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Memorandum of What Constitutes Proper Observance of Signal Tests, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    By Union Pacific Railroad. December 27, 1922. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Memorandum of What Constitutes Proper Observance of Signal Tests, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    By Union Pacific Railroad (Eastern and South-Cnetral Districts). Revised August 10, 1941. Item is in English.
- Standard Train Rule Examination, 1929; Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
  By G.E. Collingwood
  - Item 1: Standard Train Rule Examination, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    By G. E. Collingwood. 12th Edition. Item is in English.
- Pamphlets, 1941-1946; Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Miscellaneous Rulings, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Important Information Concerning the 1946 Amendments to Railroad Retirement Acts, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    By Robert J. McDonald. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: B. E. Pamphlet 20-G For Trainmasters and Train and Engine Crews, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Effective January 7, 1941. Item is in English.
- Newspapers, 1937-1956; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Rock Island No.17 Hits Freight Train, Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    By The Herington Times-Sun. Newspaper article in The Herington Times-Sun, v.4:no.11 (1937: Sept. 7). Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Engineer Tells Seeing Mirage Before Wreck, Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    By Los Angeles Examiner. Newspaper article in the Los Angeles Examiner v.53:no.44 (1956: Jan. 24). Item is in English.
  - Item 3: 14 Killed, 104 Injured as PRR Flier Wrecks at Bennington, Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    By Altoona Mirror. Newspaper article in the Altoona Mirror, v.62:no.210 (1947: Feb. 18).. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Probe Into PRR Train Wreck Begins, Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    By Atloona Mirror. Newspaper article in the Altoona Mirror, v.62:no.211 (1947: Feb. 19). Item is in English.